Tuesday is a fantasy, drama film directed by Daina Oniunas-Pusić.
A mother and her teenage daughter must confront Death when it
arrives in the form of an astonishing talking bird.
Zora, played by Julia Louis-Dreyfus.
Tuesday, played by Lola Petticrew.
Death, played by Arinzé Kene.
Nurse Billie, played by Leah Harvey.
Spike, played by Jay Simpson.
Willow, played by Ellie James.
Tuesday is a 2023 fantasy drama film written and directed by Daina O.
Pusić in her feature directorial debut.
A co-production between the United Kingdom and the United States, the film stars Julia Louis-Dreyfus and Lola Petticrew as a mother and daughter
who are guided by Death in the form of a size-altering macaw in coping with the daughter's impending death from a terminal illness.
Leah Harvey and Arinzé Kene also star.
Tuesday had its world premiere at the 50th Telluride
Film Festival on 1 September 2023.
The film was released in North America in June 2024, and
in the United Kingdom on 9 August 2024.
It received generally favourable reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.